YIXUAN (SALLY) ZHANG

Phone: 443-221-0570 | Email: sallyzhang0205@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sally-zhang-11b743b5/ | GitHub: https://github.com/banbanleelee

Portfolio: https://banbanleelee.github.io/ReactPortfolio

SUMMARY

As a full-stack web developer, I offer a unique blend of marketing and psychology expertise to optimize user experiences on the web while committing to continuous learning and expanding my technical skill set to enhance the web development process.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Server-side: NodeJS, MongoDB, Express, MySQL, Sequelize, Mongoose, Apollo, GraphQL, RESTful API
- Client-side: React.js, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Bulma, Materialize, FontAwesome, Progressive Web Apps, Insomnia
- CI/CD: Heroku, Git/GitHub, shell scripting
- Other: Scrum, agile methodology

WORK EXPERIENCE

Georgia Institute of Technology | EdX | Web Development Boot Camp Teaching Assistant

Jul 2022 - Present

- Provided guidance and tutoring, overseeing the graduation of over 70+ coding bootcamp students across two cohorts
- Collaborated with other instructional team members to disseminate coding knowledge via coding exercises and activities

Mico World Limited | Marketing Manager

Feb 2021 - Present

- Researched and analyzed user preferences for live stream content and planned weekly events, generating \$10,000 worth of
 gifting on average for each event
- Organized weekly marketing and operation performance review sessions regarding the competitive condition in the NA & EU markets, go-to-market insights for growth opportunities, and revenue and profitability goals

OutdoorMaster.com | Media Buyer

May 2020 - May 2021

- Integrated target users' interests and behavior patterns to develop advertising strategies and digital assets and achieved an average Return on Ads Spending on Facebook Ads Manager of 3.5
- Communicated and collaborated with various internal stakeholders to enhance the efficiency of advertisement delivery, with an average of merely 24-hour turnaround time

World Health Ambassador | Caspio Developer

Sep 2019 - Aug 2020

- Built and deployed database web forms on Caspio software to collect and manage user and activity data
- Wrote 90% of the code in HTML, delivered on time and under budget, and received highly positive feedback from managers

PROJECTS

Honey Bee Music

https://github.com/banbanleelee/HoneyBee

A Discord Music Player Bot

July 2022

- Integrated Discord Bot API and YouTube API with JavaScript to enable user music control commands
- Deployed on Heroku for 24/7 live hosting on Discord and benefited more than 20 users

Deal LifterA Coupon-sharing Website, **Georgia Institute of Technology Coding Bootcamp**

https://github.com/banbanleelee/DealLifter

output statute of the state of

June 2022

- Used MERN (MongoDB, Express, React, Node) stack and led the development project group: wrote 60% of the code; reviewed the other 40%
- Used React.js to develop front-end components and pages, including user dashboard, deals, search bar, etc.
- Used GraphQL, MongoDB, Mongoose ODM, and Sequelize to manage data, models, and user requests
- Employed JSON Web Tokens and Bcrypt to enable user registration and log-in with secure credentials

Movie Hunters A Movie Search Engine, Georgia Institute of Technology Coding Bootcamp

https://github.com/banbanleelee/MovieHunter Feb 2022

English, Good and Annual Control of the Montage Country Brown and the Control of the Control of

- Implemented HTML and CSS (BootStrap and FontAwesome libraries) to build a responsive user interface
- Utilized JavaScript and jQuery to conduct API requests from The Movie Database API and The IMDB API to collect and present movie information based on user searches and popularity
- Applied Scrum methodology to collaborate with a team of four people to ship in only 1 week

EDUCATION

Coding Boot Camp Certificate | Georgia Institute of Technology

Atlanta, GA | 2022

M.S. in Marketing | *The Johns Hopkins University*

Baltimore, MD | 2019

B.A. in Business, B.A. in Psychology | *Brandeis University*

Waltham, MA | 2017